Oh, good morning, my sunshine.
[kisses]
[groaning]
[chuckles]
A candle with no cake?
Is that what that is?
A cake made of light and human warmth.
A recipe from Mother Moon.
I helped her make it.
[singing "Happy Birthday"]
Cheers to Vicenza!
Oh, happy birthday, sweetheart.
Thank you, Mom.
Eighteen translation movements
of the Earth.
Eighteen years.
Now your daughter is an adult.
Oh, my Goddess! What did you wish for?
To know who my dad is, obviously.
Oh, sweetie-pie…
Even on your 18th birthday, you're making
that same old wish you always make?
Yes!
-Don't you think it's a big deal?
-Mm-mm.
Don't you know
how important this is to me?
Of course I do, sweetie-pie.
And you still don't think it's a big deal,
that I want to know who my father is?
No, no, no. Not even a little bit.
[scoffs]
You think you're always right, don't you?
But I am, darling!
Come on, Mom.
You know I have the right to know.
Trust me, it's not the right time.
The moon's not aligned with Jupiter.
Gosh! You're the most
insensitive person, you know?
Um, Mommy needs
to talk to you, sweetheart.
I have nothing to say.
Okay, you just listen.
I'll do the talking.
-I had a dream…
-Oh, please!
No, I won't make you hug any goats.
Twelve goats, Mom!
You made me hug 12 goats!
Yeah, 12 goats, whatever, it's not that.
Mommy dreamt with a letter.
The letter "I" for a country.
So I thought…
Iran? Iraq? Ireland? Italy?
But I know, I can feel it. It's India.
You know I can feel this kind of stuff.
Yeah, I know, Mom.
But couldn't it be, I don't know,
uh, Israel? Iceland? Ivory Coast?
Uh, no. It's India for sure.
I can feel something is there.
-Will you come with me?
-Is Dad there?
No.
Uh, then, no. Thank you.
You know what, Mom?
I think there's something
for you to learn in India,
and it'll be good for us
to take a break from each other.
Vicenza Shakti Pravananda Oxalá
Sarahara Zalala da Silva.
Is this how you speak to your mother?
Or even worse, of India?
'Cause Mommy already taught you
we have to respect India.
India is a state of mind,
a quantum consciousness.
-It's there, inside you. Inside me.
-Mm-hmm.
-Inside all of us.
-[groans]
-[door opens]
-Vicenza!
[door closes]
[indistinct chattering]
-[man] Happy birthday, Vicenza.
-[man 2] Happy birthday.
Thank you.
-Happy birthday, Vicenza!
-Happy birthday!
Thank you, girls! [chuckling]
-[men and women] Happy birthday, Vicenza!
-In gratitude!
-Happy birthday, Vicenza.
Happy birthday, Vicenza!
-Oh…
-Thank you.
-[man 3] Happy birthday, Vicenza.
-[man and woman] Happy birthday, Vicenza!
-In gratitude.
-Happy birthday, Vicenza.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday, Vicenza!
Aw, thank you!
-I knew I would find you here!
-[gasps]
[both laughing]
Happy birthday, Vicenza!
I wish you many moons! Millions of moons!
[woman chuckling]
I got you a little something.
Thank you, Mother Moon!
Look, I got you some aloe,
spinach, and taro too.
You need to moisturize your hair.
It's not shining, my love.
-It needs to shine.
-Yeah.
[Mother Moon] Is that you?
Yes. I'm trying to finish it,
but it's getting tough.
You have to know yourself better
be able to make a self-portrait.
You're right, Mother Moon.
But how can I know myself better
if I don't even know my father?
Can you talk to Mom?
I've talked to her a thousand times.
But you know how Raion is.
She won't listen to anyone
when it comes to this subject.
[kisses]
[thunder crashing]
-Oh, Mom!
-My little sweetie-pie!
[kisses]
Oh, Mom. Safe travels.
Take care, okay?
Of course. Oh, my love,
I'm gonna miss you so much!
Me too.
-[Mother Moon] Raion!
-[Raion] Hi!
Oh, Mother Moon!
Get her safely to the airport, okay?
Let's go, I'll take care of her.
But we're late, kid! Super behind!
Hold on. Give me just a minute, please.
Blessed be the Moroccan angels,
the shamanic healing,
the odorless Erê.
And bless the nature
that takes care of all of that.
-Our whole orientation lies with it.
--Perfect.
[chuckles]
-Bless the lettuce sprout!
-[chuckling]
-One more thing.
-Mm-hmm.
If you feel the necessity
to do something insane, sweetheart,
and listen well, I didn't say "desire,"
I said "necessity"--
then listen to your heart.
Because if your heart,
and only your heart,
compels you to insanity…
-Then go, hold tight to Ganesha and go.
-Okay!
Oh, my love.
[kisses]
[engine revving]
[Raion] I love you so much, sweetie!
Bye!
[exhales]
-[gasps]
-[frame clatters]
RIO, CARNIVAL OF 2002
SANTA TERESA'S TROUPE, RAION AND PACO
"Santa Teresa's Troupe. Raion and Paco."
[exhales]
[sighs]
[bugs chittering]
[chuckles softly]
["Casa" by Nina Fernandes playing]
COSMIC UNIVERSE
FOR SALE
[man] How much is it?
[gasps] Three hundred. Thank you.
-A ticket to Rio de Janeiro, please.
-Okay.
Go straight down that way.
Hey, ma'am?
Why are people throwing money at me?
What?
-Aren't you begging?
-No!
Not that I don't need money…
Do you know where Santa Teresa is?
-In gratitude!
-Good luck!
With all my heart.
[boy] Amoeba party! Woo-hoo!
-What's up? Check out the Naked Amoeba.
-The party!
-[boy] In two weeks!
-[boy 2] We'll have music!
Bring family, friends. You'll love it!
Excuse me. Naked Amoeba's party.
It's in two weeks, okay?
[boy 2] We're gonna have music.
I'll be playing too.
Yeah, other people will play too.
Hey, guys, what's up?
Naked Amoeba's party, okay?
It's in two weeks.
-We're gonna have music.
-Naked Amoeba. In two weeks.
[boy] It'll be like a rave.
[boy 2] Yeah, we'll have live music!
[boy] Naked Amoeba!
-Check out the Amoeba Party!
-[girl] Check the party out!
[girl 2] Whoa!
Pay attention to what you're doing!
-[boy] Sorry.
-[girl 2] You almost dropped me.
-I know. Sorry.
-[girl 2] Dude, pay attention.
-Jesus, what are you looking at?
-Nothing, nothing.
-Excuse me, hi.
-Hi.
-Where this is address?
-It's here.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
PACO'S STUDIO
[intercom buzzes]
[exhales]
Yes? What do you want
so early in the morning?
[chuckles] It's 2:15 p.m.
Good afternoon!
Oh, boy. She's a hugger.
Um… I'm, uh, looking for Paco.
Oh, Paco. Is it about classes?
-Yes! It's about classes!
-Great. Come on in.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Hold on! Wait, not so fast. Hold on.
Paco!
What's with all the yelling, Josie?
It's Jade. Ja-de.
[Paco] Yeah, Jade.
[refrigerator opens]
Pssst. That girl wants to talk to you.
-Who is she?
-I have no idea.
[groans]
-Hey, how are you?
-Hey, Paco.
I'm here to discuss classes with you.
But today's a Saturday.
-It's Saturday.
-It's just, I came a long way to meet you.
Listen, you come back on Monday,
and we'll talk, okay?
Oh, Paco. I need your help for a second.
Could you come here?
Just a second. Stay there.
He'll be right back, okay?
Look, I don't mean to pry, but…
you haven't sold a painting in a while.
These classes
have been helping you make ends meet.
Let me tell you a secret,
I don't like teaching.
I hate doing push-ups, but I do them.
That's life.
[Paco sighs]
Go over there. Talk to her.
Go.
Look at her.
-You said you came a long way?
-Ten hours on the bus.
I'll make an exception for you.
Just give me a minute to, uh…
wash my face.
Vicenza!
My name is Vicenza.
It's the mix of "Vicente" and "Zana,"
my maternal grandparents.
[Paco scoffs]
[chuckles]
Don't touch that.
Don't touch that, okay?
Tell me, why do you want to have classes?
It's because I'm having trouble
with my self-portrait.
-I think I've got a creative block.
-Welcome to the club.
I haven't painted anything in five years.
-Really?
-Really.
It happens, though.
Let me tell you,
I'm not the most patient person.
So to teach, I handpick my students,
the ones I think are worth it.
Do you have anything to show me?
No, but I can draw something quickly.
-Don't worry about it.
-It's okay.
No, look, you don't have to.
Listen to me.
You really don't have to, okay?
-Is that me?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay. So you can come back on Monday.
Okay, let's go.
I'll walk you to the door. Come on.
-Uh, Paco?
-Mm-hmm?
I'm Raion's daughter.
Raion?
[chuckling]
Your mom's Raion?
Look at that!
Do you remember this Carnival?
[Paco] I do.
Of course I remember. [chuckles]
-You were 30 years old, right?
-Yeah.
I think so, 30.
And right now you're 48.
Yes, but it doesn't show, right?
People usually think I'm 40, tops.
Raion…
It's gotta be the beard.
People lie, Paco.
What about Raion? Is she still living
in that community? The Namaste?
Cosmic Universe. Mm-hmm.
Mm.
That's pretty sweet.
I might be your daughter, Paco.
[door opens]
-[Jade] Paco.
-[door closes]
Look, I can't wait for you, okay?
I'm out.
Bye, little doll.
-Bye.
-So cute. Bye.
[kisses]
Call me, okay?
You know what? I'll call you.
[footsteps fade]
So how long are you planning
to stand there speechless?
I need to know if I should stay here,
or if I should get some water, tea…
No, it's just, uh…
[chuckling nervously]
Raion never said anything.
She never reached out…
Can I talk to her?
She's in India, totally out of reach.
[Paco hyperventilating]
-I see.
-Can I get you anything?
-Are you okay?
-A pillow.
-Huh?
-A pillow. Just a pillow.
-Okay.
-[Paco panting]
[groaning]
I'm going out. I'm going out.
-Where to?
-I don't know.
Can I go with you?
-Where's your mother staying, again?
-I don't know.
-What about you? Where are you staying?
-Nowhere.
God, it gets worse.
Come, I'll take you to a place nearby.
But wait! My bag, Paco!
I got it, I got it.
Got it, got it, got it.
I got it! There it is.
-Now let's go!
-Calm down!
Breathe.
I just wanted to meet you.
It's a pleasure. Shall we?
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go. Go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
-[Paco] Arthur!
-[Arthur] Hey!
I'm here!
-Hey, Arthur. Everything good?
-Mm!
-Good.
-Good?
-This is, uh…
-Vicenza.
Vicenza, Arthur.
-Arthur, Vicenza.
-How are you?
Vicenza needs our help.
Do you have a room?
Any room available?
I'll pay you later.
[indistinct conversation continues]
-[Paco] Vicenza? Vicenza.
-Mm?
-Write my number down.
-I didn't bring my phone.
-What?
-I don't use it much, I didn't bring it.
She doesn't use her phone.
Uh, call me if you need me.
Okay? Arthur knows where to find me.
So, bye-bye. Bye!
[chuckles] Look, don't worry.
He's always like that.
Welcome to our humble home.
-Thank you.
-Come, I'll show you to your room.
[intercom buzzes]
[Paco] Coming!
-What, it's Monday already?
-No.
I came to see if you wanted me
to make you some breakfast.
So we can learn a bit about each other.
Here. You'll feel better.
[groans]
You're trying to kill me.
Trust me. It's good for you.
[groaning]
-Mmm.
-[groaning]
[gagging]
This juice is good for headaches,
stomach aches, stress…
Okay. If I drink it,
will you be nice and quiet?
-Nice and quiet.
-Awesome.
Oh.
Before I forget…
I dug around to find a phone.
It's my old cell phone.
-Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
If you have to speak to me,
just give me a call. There you go.
[groaning]
-Do you know how to use it?
-Of course.
But this one is better than mine.
[groaning]
[Paco muttering]
Fine, I get it. You want to sleep,
so you want me to go.
-Yes. Think you could?
-Mm-hmm.
Fantastic.
-In that case, we can talk later, okay?
-Sure.
Ah, there you go.
Mm! The juice!
["Tão Bem" by Melim playing]
[chuckles]
You're welcome.
"You're welcome"?
You're welcome for what?
Did I happen to say
you could go through my stuff?
-Did I?
-[bucket clatters]
Sorry, I…
What did you do to my house, huh?
What's this?
Look at my desk!
-Weren't you leaving?
-Paco, I was just trying to help.
Did I ask for your help?
No, but I thought…
I thought all of that mess
was blocking your inspiration.
Blocking my inspiration?
Now the energy will be able to flow.
The creativity will come back! You'll see!
I'll show you how I get energy to flow.
Go away!
[papers rustle]
-[boy singing]
-[music playing]
We'll practice till day of the party.
Sounds good? Thanks, guys.
-Hey!
-You weren't here earlier, right?
I wasn't. So you're
the new guest, I'm assuming.
Cool! [chuckling]
-You're already dressed for the Carnival!
-No.
No? I'm sorry.
I'm not the best
when it comes to talking to girls.
Especially when they're so pretty.
-I mean, no.
-[chuckling]
Yeah. Not that you're not pretty.
-You're gorgeous, actually.
-[chuckles]
I'm Arthur's grandson.
Arthur is my grandpa, you know?
Of course, if I'm his grandson,
he's obviously…
[chuckles] It's a pleasure. Cadu.
Vicenza.
How can I help you, Vicenza?
Do you need anything?
Yo, Cadu. I found my instrument
for the troupe. The tuba.
Cool, but I'm in the middle
of something here.
You can listen too. Check this out.
[tooting out of tune]
It's just a little clogged,
but I'll fix it.
So what do you think?
-Why not start with something simpler?
-Why? You didn't like it?
-I did!
-Really?
Who's the weirdo in the costume?
One, my name is Vicenza.
Two, this is not a costume.
And three,
you suck at playing the tuba.
You're, like, the worst tuba player
I've ever heard.
And I don't understand
why someone would tell you otherwise.
[kisses]
So Vicenza, I'm gonna go, okay?
If you want to get my number
from Cadu, Prin-cenza…
I could give you some tuba lessons and…
[toots]
Yeah.
Cadu, give her my number, okay?
Thanks. Ah.
Let me tell you something serious.
Cadu, pay attention.
This thing you're doing,
always telling the truth…
It's rare nowadays, right?
It's like a gift.
When you have a gift,
share it with the world.
If you don't,
you know what happens, don't you?
-What?
-It bites you. Life's a snake!
[hisses] Sorry.
[kisses]
Thanks. Big Nose, give me that drum
so I can make some noise!
-"Life's a snake. Life makes you pay."
-[both chuckle]
That's Nando, yeah. He's a character.
You talked about me,
but you're quite handsome too.
You think?
[chuckling] Thank you.
-I've never heard that from a girl before.
-You sure?
I'm sure.
I wish that was caught on camera
because nobody will believe me.
Uh, hey weirdo.
I see you trying
to get close to my brother,
but everyone knows Paco's broke.
How's he paying for your stay?
What's this, Betina?
Is this how you talk to people?
She's right. I don't wanna stay here
at Paco's expense.
But that doesn't justify your behavior.
Shall we try again?
Betina, this is Vicenza.
Vicenza, this is my sister Betina.
-Where's the money?
-She's the treasurer.
-You can tell, right?
-Yeah.
Look, I don't have money right now,
but I can find another way to pay.
I could, um…
I could teach yoga, for example.
I could also fix things,
I could clean, or paint, cook…
-Do you know how to sew?
-I'm a great seamstress.
See? Wonderful! She can sew our sign!
-Sure, and she can fix the sink too!
-Mm-hmm.
No fixing the sink.
You know that's impossible, Betina.
Nothing is impossible for Vicenza.
-Show me the sink.
-[Betina chuckles]
-Have you been living here long?
-Since my parents died.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Don't worry. No problem.
When I think about it,
ten years is a long time,
living with my grandpa and my sister.
And your grandma?
My grandma…
-I haven't seen her in five, six years.
-Oh, jeez.
No, no. It's all good. Don't worry.
She left 'cause she wanted to.
She left my grandpa tons of debt,
she stole…
everything the troupe had.
He's never gotten over that.
So that means he fills up the place
with guests and hosts classes
as a way to pay his debts
and to keep his mind busy, right?
Exactly. And that's why Betina and I
want to throw a party for the troupe.
I don't know,
to try to cheer him up a little.
I mean, I guess we're going for
a modern vibe or something.
We don't want to just go with,
um, samba or Carnival songs.
Betina thinks it's old-fashioned,
everyone does that.
We want to try something new,
with a bit of an electronic vibe.
-[groans]
-I know, I don't like the idea either.
But I was outvoted, you know?
We're even throwing a rave to raise money.
-It's gonna be cool.
-What's up, Cadu?
Lucinha! How are you doing?
-Everything good?
-I missed you!
Lucinha, Vicenza. Vicenza, Lucinha.
-Hi.
-How are you?
[Cadu] She's staying here with us.
Oh my, is there going to be
a costume party?
No, this is what I wear.
Aw, you're so cute.
You're a real hippie, huh?
[gasps] You're hooking up with Cadu, huh?
-No, Lucinha. It's not that. She…
-Shush! Just be grateful, okay?
This guy here can't flirt
to save his life.
So, seeing Little Cadu with someone
is a miracle.
It's a sign that things work out
when we have enough faith.
Hallelujah, Lord!
Have you ever seen a rave
with poor lighting?
No, of course you haven't!
Come on, man.
No, look,  I don't care!
I need more lights, period!
Hey, Betina. Look what I made.
Oh, it's looking good!
-I like it.
-Thanks.
-You did this?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, that looks pretty!
Vicenza.
Someone's here to see you.
You think we can talk?
You have every reason to be mad at me.
I'm glad you know that.
Yeah…
I shouldn't ever
talk to you like that. Ever.
Yeah… not that it could justify
how rude I was, you know,
not even in the slightest,
of course, but my life's not…
you know, really good right now.
Actually, it's pretty bad right now.
I've been, uh…
I've been frustrated, I've been angry.
It's been ages since I felt
any inspiration, I'm broke.
I don't have anything.
So, then I think I… I ended up…
taking it out on you,
with all this stuff I'm dealing with.
Forgive me.
I have to apologize to you as well.
I shouldn't have messed with your things.
Yeah, but they actually said
they miss you.
My things.
[both chuckle]
Seriously, will you forgive me?
Of course.
I want to just start over from scratch.
You know, just pretend nothing happened
and we just start over.
-Wanna go for a walk with me?
-A walk?
-Yeah!
-Aw, how cute!
Let's do it. Let's go for a walk.
-For real?
-Mm-hmm.
-So go change.
-Okay.
-[Paco] Your mother is really special.
-I know.
[Paco] Very special.
I remember her well.
She came to Santa Teresa for a retreat
and stayed through Carnival.
We weren't together for long.
We hung out for like three weeks.
Not even a month.
She really loved
this place where I'm taking you.
-And I think you'll like it too.
-[chuckles]
Oh!
Ah!
-That's amazing.
-[chuckles]
So tell me, what are you planning to do,
with all this
"might be your father" thing?
I told you.
I just want to get to know you.
-That's what we're doing now, right?
-Yes.
-That's why we're here.
-Mm-hmm.
-Do you have any kids?
-No.
-I've never wanted any.
-Why?
Raising a child is serious business,
it's really complex.
I never thought I was
cut out to be a father.
You know, I never thought
I would be responsible enough
to raise someone.
It's pretty responsible of you
to say that.
[chuckles]
It's so crazy, isn't it? The Universe
drops a daughter on you out of nowhere.
[both chuckle]
It's so crazy. Insane.
But I'm really digging it.
Majorly.
[Paco groans]
I've always dreamt of eating
a nice burger with some soda.
[chuckling]
-How come? Have you never had one?
-Mm-mm.
I've never eaten meat.
[groans] Why didn't you say something?
We could've gone somewhere else.
Mm-mm!
I really wanted to try it.
Your favorite hamburger.
And when you were talking about it,
you were so excited,
I didn't want to disappoint you.
-Is it good?
-It tastes like armpits.
-[chuckling]
-But it's good, isn't it?
Look.
After this, I'll take you
to see the statue of Drummond.
Do you know where it is?
In Copacabana, near Tower Six…
[Vicenza grunting]
-[Paco] Are you okay?
-No!
But I will be!
[Paco] Vicenza?
[Vicenza retching]
Vicenza?
-[Vicenza] Yeah?
-Are... you okay?
[Vicenza burping] No!
[Paco] I really don't have anything.
Only water, expired yogurt, eggs and soda.
You seriously don't have anything
to make tea in this house?
-Yeah, sorry.
-Peppermint?
Or lemongrass? Or ginger? Even Chamomile?
-Tell me more.
-About teas?
Yeah.
Um…
Fennel?
Or bilberry? Or chaga? Or hibiscus?
Are you going to paint?
[Paco] Keep talking, keep talking.
Mulungu.
Or Guaçatonga!
Espinheira santa!
-Star anise.
Here.
See how tidying up the place helped?
Ah. You think that tidying up the place
is what helped me?
[laughing]
Mmm!
You wanna paint together?
-I've never painted with someone else.
-Me neither.
Wanna try?
-Let's do it.
-Come on, come on!
["Nessa Paz Eu Vou" by Tiago Iorc playing]
A stroke just like this.
Release your arms.
-It's great.
-Mm-hmm.
Do you have a boyfriend
at the Cosmic Universe?
Girlfriend?
A partner?
-[Vicenza chuckling]
-Huh?
No?
Let's go back to painting.
Painting.
[sighs]
[exhales]
Cadu!
-Cadu!
-Yeah. What's up, Vicenza?
I found something
that might change my life.
Do you know this guy?
[Arthur] Of course!
It's Giovanne. He used to live here.
I mean, he's been gone
for a long time, but…
but he and Paco were close friends.
Do you remember his last name?
His surname was Italian.
Pavaro… No, not Pavarotti.
It starts with B… Ah!
-Benizatto!
-Benizatto.
"Giovanne Benizatto with double T,"
as he used to say. That's him.
And you never heard anything from him?
Look, it's been a while.
Someone once told me he was working
in the financial market,
dealing with stocks and stuff.
So, he might work at Leader Bank?
Yes. If he's not the owner.
So that's it. I found it.
I found where he works.
-Can you take me there?
-[Cadu] Sure.
Thank you, Pop.
-God bless you both.
-Thanks.
[Cadu] Vicenza,
if you don't mind me asking,
why is it so important
for you to meet this Giovanne?
-Because he could be my father.
-Ah.
I could have sworn Paco was my father.
Wait a minute. Paco?
So, I found a picture
that my mother's been hiding
since Carnival of 2002, of her and Paco.
That's the reason I came here.
Then I found out
Giovanne was also with my mom
during the same Carnival.
And they were even kissing
in the photo I found of them.
While in the picture of my mom with Paco,
they're just hugging.
I have to meet him, Cadu.
You will. You will meet him.
Trust me, I promise I will help you.
It'll be an honor.
Did you think about
how you're gonna get in?
[Vicenza] Why? Can't I just walk in?
No, there's-- there's security and…
-Also, there's a little--
-Cadu, I'm following my heart. Relax.
When I do that, things work out for me.
Always. In a very crazy way.
But it shouldn't go wrong now, right?
Right.
Good morning. Name, please.
Vicenza Shakti Pravananda
Sarahara Oxalá Zalala da Silva.
Silva. Okay.
Uh, where are you going?
Uh, I'm heading to Leader Bank.
Okay, which floor?
No idea.
What? How can I announce you're here?
Could you not announce it?
Of course not. I'm being paid to announce.
Uh… Ma'am, the person
I came to see doesn't know I exist,
and I didn't know
about his existence either.
-Do you understand?
-No.
I came here to meet my father.
[gasps]
-What's his name?
-Giovanne Benizatto.
[keys clacking]
Do you know him?
I don't know him.
But you are going to!
[woman sniffs]
-Picture.
-With me?
No, here.
[chuckles]
Great.
Good luck to you.
On the tenth floor, room 1002.
In gratitude.
-In gratitude right back at ya!
-[chuckles]
-[turnstile clacks]
-[beeps]
Can I help you?
[Vicenza] Um…
[beeps]
Thank you.
No problem.
[female voice] Going up.
Ten!
[beeps]
[female voice] First floor.
Ten!
[man] Ten.
[elevator dings]
[female voice] Going up.
Wow, this is cool. This box flies.
[elevator dings]
Can I help you?
-Hi. I'm looking for Giovanne Benizatto.
-Over there.
I know. I understand, Mr. Victor.
Lower your voice when you talk to me.
I told you, you could lose money.
[shouting] Lower your voice to talk to me!
-Can I help you? Looking for someone?
-You.
-For me? And who are you?
-Vicenza.
I'm Raion's daughter.
-[scoffs] Raion?
-Mm-hmm.
So long since I heard from your mom.
Uh, have a seat.
And how is she?
Oh, you know, she's good.
So, I came here because--
You're in a bad financial situation
and you came here for advice.
[both chuckle]
Listen, you know I charge
a small fortune to do this,
but for you, I'll do it for free.
For Raion.
You know I had a little fling
with your mom, right? [chuckles]
-Oh, wow.
-Let's start.
What's your name, cutie?
Uh, Vicenza Shakti Pravananda Oxalá
Sarahara Zalala da Silva.
Silva.
Mother's name. Raion…
-Silva.
Father's name?
I don't have a father.
Okay.
Date of birth?
Uh, November 8th, 2002.
The same year
you happened to meet my mom.
[chuckling]
You could be my daughter. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
You could be my daughter?
-That's why you're here?
-Yes.
-Daughter?
-Daughter.
Daughter!
[grunts]
I, uh… I think that…
I think that we need to talk, right?
["Cabelo de Anjo"
by Melim & Lulu Santos playing]
Do you wanna grab something to eat?
Are you hungry?
I'm actually always hungry.
But I don't want to eat at a restaurant.
A homemade meal would be awesome.
So I know exactly where to take you.
Come here.
Taxi!
[Vicenza] Hi!
Wow!
[Giovanne] Can you give me a hand?
-Mm-hmm.
-Here you go.
[sighs]
It's funny.
My stepsons never cooked with me.
I mean, ex-stepsons.
And have you ever invited them
to cook with you?
Yeah.
I mean, I think I have.
-[chuckles]
-Got it.
Okay. Careful here.
How many stepsons do you have?
Two. Guilherme and Rael.
Are they nice?
They're the coolest guys I've ever met.
-How long have you been divorced?
-Two years.
Mmm.
-Are you still friends with their mother?
-With Marta?
Yes, yes. Marta is…
a good friend of mine.
[both laughing]
Thanks.
[man] Ohm…
The most important thing in life
is to breathe.
Breath is peace, breath is water…
Hear me out, don't you think it's crazy
for us to come all the way to India
to watch a guy in Los Angeles
on a Skype call?
He's not sweating like a pig over here.
With these bugs.
And we can't even kill the flies.
It's not spiritually evolved to kill them.
-Shh!
[man] Let's breathe like the beetle.
Let's try! Hard! Very hard!
[inhales]
Ohm…
Tell me, why did it take you so long
to look for me?
Because my mom went to India,
so this was the first time I could escape.
What do you mean, escape?
Escape?
Your mom doesn't know you're here?
Relax, relax.
I came following my heart.
It's all good.
No, it's not.
We'll have to call your mom right now!
No way, I'm sorry. She's way out of reach.
[scoffs]
So you had to run away?
Raion doesn't want you to meet me?
Actually, she didn't want to talk
about you or anyone.
All she said was, "It's not the time
for you to meet your father."
-But it never was!
-I see.
And you're sick and tired of not knowing
who your father is.
Absolutely.
Uh…
Do you want a little more tea?
No, thank you.
Actually, I think it's getting late.
-I should go.
-No, stay a little more.
It's raining.
Where are you staying?
At the headquarters of a troupe
in Santa Teresa.
-The Naked Amoeba. Do you know it?
-Come on!
I haven't been there in forever.
Why don't we do this? Look…
you sleep here tonight, in Rael's bedroom,
and tomorrow morning,
before I go to work, I'll take you there.
[phone pings]
[curtains open]
[woman] What's going on here?
-Huh? What is this?
-Calm down. I can explain.
Yeah, I think
you should explain, Giovanne.
It's not every day we come to your house,
and Rael finds Sleeping Beauty in his bed!
Listen, this is Vicenza.
She may be my daughter.
What did you say, Giovanne?
Your daughter, Giovanne?
She may be your daughter?
-Daughter?
-Calm down!
-[Marta] What do you mean?
-[Giovanne] I'll explain outside.
Calm down! Stop yelling!
-[Marta] I can't believe it!
-Are you going to live here?
-Do you play Fortnite?
-[Rael] Or FIFA?
Are you good at math?
Uh…
No, I'm not gonna live here.
I don't know those games, and…
-I'm really good at math.
-Yes!
[Marta]
Don't disrespect me in front of the kids!
[Giovanne] Stop yelling!
[Marta] You can't seriously think
that girl is your child.
How dumb are you?
Uh, boys, I need to be alone for a bit
to get changed. Can you excuse me?
-Sure.
-Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
[Marta and Giovanne arguing]
-[Marta] Are you out of your mind?
-I talked to her!
[Marta] Oh my God, wake up!
Have you thought about the huge amount
of money you have in the bank?
What about it?
This girl is clearly just thinking
about taking all of your money!
Stop! Lower your voice!
I won't! You're driving me insane.
-You're getting it all wrong.
-You're irresponsible!
I don't regret divorcing you at all!
I don't regret it either!
I wasn't gonna sit there and hear
that woman question my character.
Vicenza, I don't know why you care.
Little does she know you're an angel.
-Me? An angel? Really?
-Really.
The most beautiful angel of all.
-[chuckles]
-[phone buzzes]
Oh!
It's Paco. He wants to hang out with me.
Are you gonna mention Giovanne?
Oh, Cadu. I don't know.
I don't want to hurt him.
I'm absolutely sure if I tell him,
he'll be sad.
And I don't want to be the person
that makes Paco sad.
What about Giovanne?
You tell him about Paco then?
He's so cool.
Cadu, help me. I don't know what to do.
-[Betina] Be careful.
-I think you should tell them the truth.
You're crazy, right, Cadu?
-So you were listening?
-Betina.
Yeah, I was listening, okay?
I like a good gossip, I can't resist it.
If I were you,
I wouldn't tell either of them.
But I hate lying, Betina.
I don't even know how to.
Oh, my sweet girl. Here me out.
First, you're not gonna lie.
You're gonna omit.
And second,
why would you risk everything
you're creating with both of them? Huh?
["Felicidade" by Marcelo Jeneci playing]
[phone buzzes]
[Vicenza] Here.
I wanted to apologize.
For Marta, for myself.
-I never imagined that…
-It's all right.
Sometimes we say stuff
without thinking, right?
But do you forgive me?
I forgive you. Where are the boys?
Uh, I asked them to come next week.
I needed some time to be alone.
My head is all over the place
with the chance of having a daughter.
[chuckles]
[kisses]
[phone pings]
Yes, it does.
You're breathing right, huh, Mr. Paco!
You've learned!
I have a very good teacher.
I'll give you her number later.
[both chuckle]
[kisses]
Align it with your shoulder.
See, look. Same with this arm.
[phone pings]
Smell. Try it.
Vi, I hope it's okay to ask,
but are you not telling Paco or Giovanne?
[groans] I can't do it, Cadu.
I don't want to hurt them, you know?
I see. And what does your heart tell you?
You always listen to it.
Sometimes my heart is sure it's Paco,
but then it thinks it's Giovanne.
Then why don't you take a DNA test?
That'll do it. You know
what a DNA test is, don't you?
Of course I do, Cadu!
I don't live under a rock.
But doesn't it cost a fortune?
No, no. Not anymore, I guess.
It did in the past.
But it's pretty cheap nowadays,
so everyone can do it.
I think there's a website…
No, it's an app. No, a website.
You put in all the info. Check it out.
You just need to collect a few things,
like blood, saliva, hair…
See? You just…
Vi!
Vi! Careful, careful!
-When you get to the top, jump.
-Jump?
No, not this way, that way.
When you get there, you jump.
Wait, I'll help you. Hold on.
-I'm almost there.
-Hold on, yeah.
Jump. There we go.
-[Vicenza] Oh, that's cool!
-[Cadu] Sorry.
-[Cadu] Vi!
-There's another one!
[Cadu] Vicenza, wait!
Vi! Okay, calm down, I know.
It's an escalator, it's something new.
Listen, I found the website.
It says here you just need
a sample of blood, hair or saliva,
then you'll know
who's the biological father.
Vicenza, no. Enough escalators.
[Paco] Mmm.
[slurping]
[chatting indistinctly]
[Giovanne] Gotcha.
Thank you.
You should use this straw.
It's eco-friendly.
Sounds good.
Let's do this.
Mmm.
[slurping]
Here, Cadu.
Everything we need for the DNA test.
Awesome. I'll take care of it for you.
Thank you.
[kisses]
-I don't know what I'd do without you.
-[chuckles]
I don't know what I'm gonna do
when you go back home.
You're the most special girl
I've ever met, you know?
-[chuckles]
-Bro!
Listen, it's urgent.
We need to promote the rave.
Ticket sales are terrible,
and we need money
to put the parade out there, right?
Let's print flyers and distribute them.
-Awesome.
-Okay.
[Betina] Come on.
[man vocalizing] Ohm.
Ohm.
[shrieks]
[all] Shh!
My daughter's missing!
You don't understand.
My daughter. My daughter missing.
[all] Shh!
Guys, how insensitive!
I expected more from you here!
Holy moly.
How can you expect me to be zen
after this kind of news? Holy cow!
[Paco] Hey there!
-Hey.
-Look what I brought.
I'm gonna make you the juice.
-Mmm!
-For you.
[both chuckling]
It's nice.
[Vicenza] Thank you.
Look.
Amoeba party. Shall we?
Really? You want to go?
Why wouldn't I?
I'm too old for it?
[chuckles] Of course not, Paco.
[chuckles]
-Use a little more orange.
-You got it.
[scoffs]
There will be a party at your place,
and you don't even invite me, huh?
Yeah…
Giovanne, how on earth would I know
you're into electronic music?
I don't like it.
But I'm gonna love seeing
everyone else.
Especially since you're there.
Shall we?
[keys clacking]
We shall! Sure, we'll go!
Just bought the tickets.
Mmm.
[all sigh]
Guys, I really need your help with this.
I'll try to summarize it, okay?
So, I never had a father--
Oh, poor little baby girl!
…but now I have two.
-Wow, then life is good!
-[all laugh]
I'm crazy about them.
They're both really, really cool.
They even know each other.
But neither of them can know
the other could also be my dad.
And both are coming to our party.
-[all react]
-Holy cow, you're screwed, girl!
-Lucinha, girl, you're not helping.
-Sorry. I feel for her.
Okay, and what can we do
for them to not bump into each other?
[gasps] I got it! Why don't we ask
everyone to wear costumes to the rave?
Like rave meets Carnival?
-[all gasp]
-You're a genius! That's it!
We'll leave a chest with costumes
at the entrance
so if anyone doesn't bring a costume,
they just grab one.
-There's no excuse.
-Yeah! Masks, noses, wigs…
It'd make it harder
for them to recognize each other.
You rock, Lucinha.
[Lucinha] That one over there.
[indistinct chatter]
Yeah, that one on the right.
[Nando and Cadu arguing]
-I'm practicing!
-Why? You can't play it!
[Nando and Cadu continue arguing]
[woman] Beautiful!
Oh, these are all tangled!
Betina, help me out here!
Come help me, please!
Cadu is taking away my tuba!
I was practicing…
[overlapping chattering]
[chuckling]
[woman] Did you bring that?
♪ Baby, you should know the truth ♪
♪ I'm not leaving without you ♪
♪You got me feeling so cool ♪
♪ All night I'll be lovin' you… ♪
[upbeat dance music playing]
Yes! With a cat costume!
Good job on the costume, bro!
[all laughing]
Guys, the party is packed!
You guys'll be able to parade
with the troupe!
We'll be able to parade with the troupe!
I told you it would work, guys!
[both chuckling]
-[Lucinha] Betina, come here!
-Whoa, hold on a sec!
-I'm gonna show you something. Come.
-Wait.
Vicenza! Vicenza!
[both chuckling]
I was dying to see you, I have great news.
Seriously? Go ahead!
My art dealer just told me
we closed a deal on an art exhibit
of my latest works in New York.
-No! Wow!
-Yeah!
That's awesome! [chuckling]
It's all thanks to you.
You inspired me to start painting again.
Come on, it was nothing.
Congratulations… Paco!
-You're coming with me, right?
-To New York?
It wouldn't make sense for me to go alone.
Uh, of course I'll go! When are you going?
February 9th.
You okay?
It's just 'cause
the Amoeba parade is on the 9th.
And, I mean, I helped with the flyers,
I sewed the banner,
I helped with the party.
I'm doing all I can to get it out there
and to make it great, you know?
Of course.
Of course. You're happy, right?
Because you helped organize everything,
so you're happy.
Are we good?
Of course. We're good.
If you're happy, I'm happy too.
Thank you.
[muted] It's Giovanne!
Uh, Paco,
I'm gonna go deal with something.
Take a look around, enjoy the party.
I'll be right back, okay?
Woo-hoo!
Hey, Paco!
Oh, hey, Luana!
It's Lucinha, Paco!
Vicenza! You look incredible!
Thank you, Giovanne!
-You too.
-So, what do you think?
-We could add some stuff to it. Look.
-Yeah?
-This one?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here-- Oh, boy!
I think you're overdoing it.
[both chuckling]
So? How about now?
Ta-da! Do I look great or what?
Awesome!
I look like someone who's going to Disney
with his stepsons for the first time.
-[gasps] That's incredible news!
-Will you come with us?
-To Disney World? For real?
-Yeah!
-Oh, my God! Of course! Wow!
-[chuckling]
-When will you go?
-February 9th.
[chuckling nervously] Um…
[muted] Paco is here!
-Nando!
-What's up?
You scared me, Vicenza.
Uh… um… Nando, this is Giovanne.
My, uh, friend.
Giovanne, this is Nando.
He's the troupe's, uh…
I'm the main musician of the troupe.
-I play all the instruments.
-Uh…
-Giovanne adores music.
-I do?
-You like music?
-I mean, I do, but…
Play for him. [chuckling]
You know our master?
The master! This one dude…
-Yeah, a master for sure.
-A classic, right?
[Vicenza chuckling] Hey!
[Paco] Hi!
Woo-hoo!
This party's the bomb, huh?
-[chuckling]
-The party is amazing! I'm loving it!
[laughing]
Hey!
-What's up?
-Everything cool?
-Cool.
-Sweet.
-I'll have a drink, please, sir.
-What?
-It's for Betina! Thank you.
-[Paco] Huh?
It's for Betina.
I'm watching you!
-Okay, sounds good!
-You're on thin ice!
Arthur!
Huh? Paco!
Oh, you're such a pretty lady!
[both laughing]
What's up, what's up?
-Hey, Vicenza!
-Hey.
Bye, guys!
-[Giovanne] See ya.
-[blows kiss]
-What's up? Do you want a drink?
-Um, no, Vicenza,
it's just, um, I'm driving.
I shouldn't be drinking.
I think I'm gonna get water at the bar.
Yeah, I'll do that.
What's up? A sparkling water.
No, have a green juice.
[Giovanne] Green juice? Are you sure?
-[Paco] King Arthur!
-[both laughing]
I'm heading over there. See you.
[Arthur] Enjoy!
-I'll be right back, okay?
-Yeah? Okay.
[coughs]
Giovanne?
Arthur!
[both laughing]
My God! It's been too long a time!
-The Great Arthur!
-[chuckling]
Good to see you.
-So good to see you too, man.
-I'll be right back, okay?
-Go on, take care!
-Real quick. All right.
Hello? I need it now!
Hello?
-Hey, girl. Have you seen Paco?
-No, I haven't. Why?
Oh, my God.
Ugh, Cadu. I'm so tired of this.
Well, Vi, I mean,
why don't you  just come clean, then?
But I'm about to get
the test results, Cadu.
Vicenza?
Vicenza. I'm going home, okay?
-[kisses]
-Okay.
Congratulations.
-Aww.
-The party was great.
Thank you.
Yeah, it really was. Super great.
-Get inside, it's getting cold.
-But it's hot.
No, it's cold. You better get inside.
You gotta cover your shoulders
and protect your neck from the cold too.
-Okay?
-Sure.
[Paco] Okay, that's it, then.
-You should avoid the drizzle, okay?
-Sure.
You're saying sure, but you're not moving.
You gotta say "sure" then get inside!
It's like a wind tunnel out there,
so, I dunno, you'll get sick!
Like, three or four days in bed!
-Bye, Paco!
-See you, Paco!
[Paco] Bye!
[both chuckling]
Vicenza.
I'm gonna go.
-I have to wake up for work soon.
-Mm-hmm.
-I loved it.
-[Vicenza] Aw.
[kisses]
-Bye.
[Vicenza sighs]
Oh, Cadu! It all worked out!
I've never been kissed.
And I've never kissed someone
I had such strong feelings for.
And so… maybe our first kiss
should happen somewhere special.
Sure.
-Can Betina lend us her car?
-She already did.
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
[both chuckle]
-[horn honking]
-[exclaiming]
What the hell, man?
[thumping] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, man! What? Didn't you see me?
Are you insane?
Shit, you're the insane one!
Nearly ran me over!
Paco?
Giovanne?
[laughing]
Damn, it's been too long, bro!
Way too long, man!
Dude! You're doing well?
Yeah. You know, close call, but yeah.
[both chuckling]
That's a big gulp.
Get in the car. I'll drive you home.
I'll get inside, but we're not going home.
It's our little after-party!
Just a tiny one.
[Giovanne] Oh, boy. You got energy, huh?
[Paco] Nice car.
[laughing]
-[Paco] Yo, thanks for not taking me home.
-[Giovanne laughing]
Wanna go for a swim?
Still afraid of cold water?
[Giovanne]
I'm not afraid. Are you insane?
I'm terrified of it!
[both laughing]
-I'm so happy I ran into you.
-Me too.
Let's go for a swim.
[stomach gurgling]
What's wrong?
No, it's just the green juice
I had at the party.
I've got a great story to tell.
You won't believe it.
Yeah, tell me, tell me.
I'll tell you in a minute.
[gagging]
[both chuckling]
-This place is gorgeous, huh?
-Yeah, gorgeous.
Know what else is gorgeous? You.
[yelling] Oh, hey!
Get your hands off my daughter!
Get your hands off  my daughter!
Daughter? What daughter?
She's my daughter!
-Quit it, kid.
-What do you mean?
Your daughter? What's this, Vicenza?
-Calm down! I can explain!
-Hold on. How did you two meet?
-Shh!
-Shut up!
Okay.
Uh, I never knew who my father was,
then suddenly
I found myself with two dads.
-Two dads?
-What are you saying?
In the Naked Amoeba's archive,
I found photos of you two with Mom.
You just went looking for Giovanne?
-He could be my dad too!
-Why didn't you tell me about Paco?
-I didn't want to hurt you, so I--
-Hurt us? [laughing]
Hurt us? Give me a break, Vicenza.
-You were misleading us?
-She was.
-No!
-For the love of God, she was trying--
-[groaning] Shh!
-Shut up!
Look, if you ask me…
I think she's your daughter, Paco.
She's as selfish as you are.
Well, I think she's your daughter.
Insensitive.
Manipulative.
I introduced your mother to him!
-You never hooked up!
-You know nothing!
-Stop it! Both of you!
-[Paco] Shut up!
[sighs]
-So you're leaving, Paco?
-[Paco] Yeah.
-[Giovanne] You never grew up, did you?
-No, I didn't.
[Cadu] Don't worry.
-Cadu.
-Calm down.
[sobbing] I love them so much!
[sniffles] And now I've lost both of them.
You didn't. They love you very much.
But come on, I told you
this was not going to end well.
-Cadu, please leave.
-No. What--
I gotta be alone for a minute.
Go away, please.
Vicenza.
[phone ringing]
Ju!
Yes?
I'm going home.
Vicenza?
Vicenza, where were you?
Why haven't you picked up my calls?
I don't wanna talk.
Come on, I was worried,
and this is how you treat me?
You think I owe you anything, Cadu?
Yeah, I think you do.
Do you have any idea
how my mind is right now?
Do you know how it feels
to go from never having a father,
to finding one,
then finding another one,
then managing to lose
both of them right after that?
And all that's my fault.
Do you know?
No, you don't.
-Vicenza.
-Cadu.
Don't go there.
Just give her some time.
-She needs to be alone for a while.
-[door opens and closes]
Tomorrow, you two can talk then. Mm?
[keypad clicking]
[phones pinging]
♪ If I have to
I will take a boat ♪
♪ I will row for six months like a fish
Just to see you ♪
♪ There's no sea large enough ♪
♪ To scare me
To make me give up on you ♪
♪ If I have to
I will build a machine ♪
♪ Faster than doubt
More sudden than a tear ♪
♪ I will travel at full power
And in a moment of pain from missing you ♪
♪ I will be there to tell you
That I came to see you ♪
♪ I want to share ♪
♪ I want to share the good life with you ♪
Vicenza, I…
What's going on Vicenza?
Where are you going?
-I'm going home. I don't belong here.
-Huh?
My mother was right, Cadu.
I wasn't supposed to meet my dad.
Are you sure?
Are those the results?
Vicenza…
I'm sorry.
There's something going on downstairs.
You have visitors.
What's up, Cadu? See ya.
Mom?
[Raion] Oh, my love!
Oh, I missed you so much. Are you okay?
Mm-hmm, I'm okay.
[snapping fingers]
Mother Moon!
[chuckling]
Hi, everyone!
-Mom, how did you find me here?
-I'm a mother, aren't I?
I got home, then I noticed
you discovered Paco's picture,
so I put two and two together,
and came here to look for him.
Exactly. That's where I come in.
I was walking outside.
I even mistook her for you.
Then it hit me, it all made sense.
Everyone's wearing costumes.
That's Vicenza's troupe!
[all laughing]
That's exactly how it was.
But our cute moment is over now.
Vicenza, how dare you run away?
You're absolutely insane!
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't have run away.
Owning up to your mistakes
is a beautiful sign of maturity, sweetie.
And Mommy has made mistakes too.
In India, Mommy realized
that she's not that esoteric after all.
And that, even though I'm your mom,
I just can't control your life
the way I would like to control it,
unfortunately.
I learned that from the flies.
What flies?
My cutie-pie, there were so many flies.
Everywhere.
And you couldn't even scare them off.
And then, what did Mommy figure out?
That you can try to control yourself.
But other people? That's impossible.
If someone wants to kill a bunch of flies,
all we can do is to understand.
I'll be forever grateful to the flies
for being able to show me that,
contrary to what I've always said,
you have every right
to know who your father is.
What is that?
It's the DNA test I did
with Paco and Giovanne.
Giovanne as well?
Yeah, I found him too.
Oh, my love…
[kisses]
[Betina] Guys! Guys! Guys!
We're really screwed!
-What?
-The stage bus caught on fire!
Did anyone get hurt?
No, no one got hurt.
But everything was on it.
-Including the money.
-But how did that happen?
Um, it seems the stage bus I rented
couldn't handle that many lights.
Dang it, Betina.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Everything happens for a reason.
Doesn't it, Mother Moon?
-Mother Moon?
-Oh!
Of course, of course! Yeah!
Uh, I agree with you.
[Raion] Right?
[Mother Moon]
We've gotta change the energy.
So come on, everyone.
[all inhale and exhale deeply]
[snapping fingers rhythmically]
I got it, guys!
The fire was a sign.
I'm sorry, Betina,
but this fire was a sign
that the Naked Amoeba
should parade like in the good old days.
With samba, Carnival songs.
With instruments and singing,
and nothing else.
Yeah, that sounds like the Amoeba.
Good old-fashioned Carnival.
I don't know what I was thinking,
trying something new.
[Arthur] Oh, my sweet girl.
Look, listen up, I, uh…
I know everyone's a bit shaken
with all that just happened,
but Vicenza is right.
You know? Yeah. 'Cause we gotta do it
like the good old days, man!
-[laughing]
-[Arthur] Yeah!
So, you…
I want you to get every student
who can play percussion.
I got it. The teachers too, right?
You should get everyone. Yeah.
Because we're going to party
and parade in the streets.
It'll be amazing!
[all chattering in excitement]
Rejoice, my good people!
Hooray for the Naked Amoeba!
[all] Hooray!
[all cheering]
It's going to be beautiful!
-[Arthur] Yeah, it will be.
-Like you.
[chuckling]
[Mother Moon] Nice to meet you.
My pleasure. I'm Arthur. Thank you.
Mother Moon.
[kisses]
But you can call me…
Moon.
[both laughing]
[no audible dialogue]
When we get to New York,
there will be a press conference.
Then you'll have a newspaper interview.
It can be through e-mail or text.
That night isn't gonna work…
[continues inaudibly]
[doorbell chimes]
Let's go to Disney!
[low energy] Yay.
-[Marta] Good morning, Giovanne.
-Good morning.
Look after those kids, please, okay?
You got it.
[sarcastic] Yay!
Guys, guys, guys! Hear me out!
I just got off the phone
with Ivete Sangalo, and she confirmed
she is in fact not coming!
[all laugh]
But I'm here!
Let's party, people! Come on!
-My shoe came off!
-For the love of God, Guilherme!
Where did you drop it?
-Here, Betina.
-Oh, thanks.
I think there's something wrong
with the speaker. Can you check?
Of course. We'll fix it. Thanks.
Vicenza! Vicenza.
[gasps] No way!
What are you doing here?
I couldn't miss your first Carnival.
-What about the art show?
-I'll do it later.
Oh, that's wonderful! I thought
you'd never want to see me again.
Come on, that's how families are.
Families fight, argue,
but then we make up.
[both chuckle]
Vicenza!
Did you forgive me too?
Of course.
What about Disney?
Well, it looks like…
they hate Disney and love you.
I don't want to go anywhere
without you, Vicenza.
[Vicenza] Guys,
I-I really love you.
So much.
But I had to find out
which one of you is my real dad.
So, I took a DNA test and now I know.
Can you close your eyes really quick?
I just have to do something.
It's important.
All right.
Please?
Wow, my heart is…
It's almost jumping out of my throat.
Yeah, same for me.
Close your eyes.
You're trying to kill us
with the suspense, right?
Calm down, guys. You'll like it.
Paco, you can't peek.
[Paco] What is this?
Stay still. There.
So, when I say "go,"
both of you open your eyes
at the same time
and read the paper
on the other's forehead.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Three…
two…
one… go!
[both]
"Do you want to be Vicenza's father?"
-What? I don't get it.
-Yeah, me neither.
Neither of you are my dad.
I'm sorry, I don't follow.
Guys, I think that's good.
It means what I have with you two
is much stronger than any blood ties.
Because a real father
wants to be with his kid.
Look where you are,
on such an important day for you both.
What I want to have with you…
[sniffles]
It's real.
I love you, Dad.
[Paco chuckles]
Do you want to be my dad?
Do you accept being my dads?
I already feel like your dad.
It's an honor.
Aw, that's so cute,
the three of you together!
-Mom!
-[Paco] Wow.
[Raion chuckling]
-Raion!
-Hi, Paco.
-Hi, Giovanne.
-Hi, Raion. Weren't you in India?
Well, yeah.
But I had to come back
so I could talk to this piece of work.
My sweetie.
Here you go. Everything
you've always wanted to know.
Name, address
and phone number of your real father.
He never wanted to hear from you,
but I can't really keep you
from knowing him forever.
I already have a dad.
Two, actually.
Vi! Hi, everyone.
It's about to start. Coming?
Let's go.
Come on!
NAKED AMOEBA
[Original Carnival song playing]
[song ends]
[soft instrumental music plays]
[Mother Moon] We grow everything.
-Hey!
-[Raion] Hey, check it out.
It's lovely.
It's beautiful, honey.
You're really special.
Brigadeiro made of banana biomass
and 79% cocoa.
But I swear it's delicious. Paco?
No, thanks.
Wow, sweetie.
It's beautiful.
[Cadu] Paco, Giovanne.
-Psst!
-What are you doing?
You guys are unbelievable. Come on, Cadu.
-Where are you going?
-Yeah, where?
-'Cause if you need company, I'll go.
-Me too.
Yeah.
Vicenza Shakti Pravananda
Oxalá Sarahara Zalala…
da Silva Benizatto Costa.
-Respect your father.
-Fathers!
Fathers, yes. Your fathers.
On our trip to the ranch next week,
everyone will walk together.
-That's right.
-The kids, you two, Paco.
Like an excursion. My trip, my rules.
Oh, God. Go!
I'll take care of these two.
Let them make out.
-Make out? What does she mean?
-What do you mean by "make out"?
I don't think Vicenza
is old enough to make out.
-Of course not. You're right.
-Hey, I'm 18 years old!
[Paco] That's the point!
Listen, put on a coat
because it's getting colder.
A hoodie! A beanie too!
Yeah, and a, um…a scarf, a shawl,
something around your neck!
Around the neck, yeah.
-This Cadu, huh?
-[chuckling]
He is clearly a psychopath.
-Oh, come on.
-Yeah.
He doesn't cut his nails.
But he doesn't cut his nails
because he plays guitar.
You're both ridiculous, guys!
Let the girl enjoy her life!
Look at this, what a beautiful painting.
You have the best daughter in the world.
-He's got hairy legs, though.
-Oh, no.
A grown man. He's not right for her.
Musician. He's really not right for her.
He's an artist.
What's wrong with that? I'm an artist too.
-So?
-That's the point.
-What's your point?
-Nothing.
[laughing]
-Oh, you guys…
-It's karma.
Huh?
-What do you mean? Fate?
-[chuckling] Please!
["Casa" by Nina Fernandes playing]
[song ends]
[cheerful instrumental music plays]